Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Wally O'Brien papers, 1948-1988 and undated RL.11620
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Wally O'Brien papers
1948-1988 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
RL.11620
15.0 Linear Feet
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. It is headquartered in New York. Walter J. (Wally) O'Brien was an executive with JWT and JWT Group, serving in a number of offices and as Vice Chairman of the company. Collection includes texts and accompanying slides of speeches and presentations; financial and management reports, correspondence and other printed materials as well as audiovisual materials in multiple formats (videocassettes, audio cassettes and tape reels, film reels). Companies represented include Beatrice, Burger King, De Beers, Ford, Goodyear, IBM, Kellogg, Kodak, Kraft, Lord Geller Federico Einstein, Mattel, Nestle, Pepsi, Philips, Reynolds Tobacco, Rolex, Unilever and Warner-Lambert. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Arrangement
Organized into the following series: General Files; Correspondence and Memoranda; Client Files; Presentations, Writngs and Speeches; and Audiovisual Materials.
Biographical / Historical
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. It is headquartered in New York. Walter J. (Wally) O'Brien was an executive with JWT and JWT Group, serving in a number of offices and as Vice Chairman of the company.
Marquette University; joined JWT New York as copywriter 1962; Account Supervisor, London Office 1966; Director, Frankfurt Office 1969; Group Account Director, Chicago Office 1972; Senior Vice President 1975; General Manager, Chicago 1979; General Manager, New York 1982; President and Chief Operating Officer, JWT USA 1982; Vice Chairman and Director of Multinational Client Services 1984; resigned 1986; partner in O'Reilly O'Brien Clow/RSCG 1986
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research. However, original audiovisual materials are closed until use copies can be produced.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. Wally O'Brien papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2004.
Related Materials
Related Materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
J. Walter Thompson Company. Account Files
J. Walter Thompson Company. Corporate Documentation
J. Walter Thompson Company. Don Johnston papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. Herbert Eames papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. Writings and Speeches
Collection Overview
Collection includes texts and accompanying slides of speeches and presentations; financial and management reports, correspondence and other printed materials as well as audiovisual materials in multiple formats (videocassettes, audio cassettes and tape reels, film reels). Companies represented include Beatrice, Burger King, De Beers, Ford, Goodyear, IBM, Kellogg, Kodak, Kraft, Lord Geller Federico Einstein, Mattel, Nestle, Pepsi, Philips, Reynolds Tobacco, Rolex, Unilever and Warner-Lambert. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising; Advertising -- United States -- History; Advertising agencies; Advertising agencies -- United States; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; Advertising agencies -- United States -- Management; Advertising executives -- United States; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Burger King Corporation; Beatrice Foods Company; De Beers Consolidated Mines; Ford Motor Company; Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company; International Business Machines Corporation; Kellogg Company; Kraft Foods Company; Nestlé; Pepsi-Cola Company; PepsiCo, Inc.; R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company; North American Philips Co; Montres Rolex S.A.; Unilever (Firm); Warner-Lambert Company
- General Files, 1968-1987 and undated; 1
  - Advertising, 1982-1986; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Agency commitment to clients, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Andy Awards, 1985-1987 (Box 1)
  - Articles, 1968-1985; 5 folders (Box 1)
  - Articles, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Asia-Pacific, 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Asia-Pacific--China, 1985 (Box 2)
  - Asia-Pacific--Far East, 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Asia-Pacific--Japan, 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Asia-Pacific Media Forum, 1985 (Box 2)
  - Canada, 1986 (Box 2)
  - Client planning budgets, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Credentials book, 1985 (Box 2)
  - Europe, 1983-1986; 4 folders (Box 2)
  - Europe, 1983-1986 (Box 3)
  - Hill & Knowlton, 1983-1985 (Box 3)
  - Hill & Knowlton, LGFE (Lord Geller Federico & Einstein) and MRB Group profiles, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Ireland, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Itineraries, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - James Webb Young Fund/Board of Trustees, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - JWT Group, 1984-1987 (Box 3)
  - JWT USA operating costs, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Latin America, 1983-1985 (Box 3)
  - Marketing philosophies, undated (Box 3)
  - Multinational background material, 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Multinational booklet, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Multinational budgeting, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Multinational business building, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Multinational client development, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Multinational Client Service Operating Review, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Multinational Client Services 1986 Headquarters Recommendation, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Multinational Client Services Action Plan proposal 1986, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Multinational Client Services Headquarter Financial Review, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Multinational coordination, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Multinational creative teams, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Multinational finances, 1983-1985 (Box 4)
  - Multinational meeting agreement, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Multinational meetings, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Multinational meetings with Denis Lanigan, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Multinational planning, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Multinational planning budget results, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Multinational program, undated (Box 4)
  - Multinational review, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - New business: Food, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Professional Development at JWT, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Retail Advertising Conference, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Selection Committee, Chicago Advertising Person of the Year, 1982 (Box 5)
  - T-Plan, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Top 20 worldwide clients, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Travel, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Worldwide Clients booklet, undated (Box 5)
  - Worldwide Client Service Director, 1985; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Worldwide Client Service Directors' Meetings, 1984-1985; 3 folders (Box 5)
  - Worldwide Client Service Review, 1985; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Worldwide Client Services booklet, undated (Box 5)
- Correspondence and Memoranda, 1978-1988 and undated; 2
  - Advertising Age survey, 1982-1985 (Box 6)
  - Assignments, 1983-1988 (Box 6)
  - Awards, 1982-1988; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Booz Allen & Hamilton, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Cableshop, 1978-1987 (Box 6)
  - Chronological file, 1984-1985; 4 folders (Box 6)
  - Chronological file, 1985; 8 folders (Box 7)
  - Chronological file, 1986; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Clients A-P, 1982-1987; 14 folders (Box 8)
  - Clients R-W, 1982-1987; 6 folders (Box 9)
  - Compensation agreements, 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - Congratulatory letters, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - Creative Directors, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Desk-to-desk memos, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - Doug Richardson, 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - EPCOT Conference, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Evaluations and reviews, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - Finances, 1982-1987; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - George Berry, 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - Holiday planning, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - Jack Scollay, 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Joe Sasernick, 1983 (Box 10)
  - JWT USA General Managers, 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Lansdowne Advertising, undated (Box 10)
  - Media, 1980-1984 (Box 10)
  - Meetings, 1982-1985 (Box 10)
  - Multinational, 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - New business, 1982-1987 (Box 10)
  - Office location, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Personal, 1982-1984 (Box 10)
  - Programs, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Recommendations, 1983-1984 (Box 10)
  - Robin Restall transfers, 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - Sadler Wells Royal Ballet, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Staff, 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Task forces, 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Thanks, 1982-1984 (Box 11)
  - Tom Veres, 1985-1987 (Box 11)
  - Wolf Lieschke, 1984 (Box 11)
  - World Advertising Review (publication), 1985 (Box 11)
  - Young and Rubicam, 1985 (Box 11)
- Client Files, 1948-1986 and undated; 3
  - 3M, 1985 (Box 12)
  - Activision, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Adolph Coors, 1982-1984 (Box 12)
  - Bacardi, 1984-1986 (Box 12)
  - Baskin Robbins, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Beatrice, 1983-1985; 3 folders (Box 12)
  - Black and Decker, 1983-1985; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Burger King, 1982-1985; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Burger King--Africa, 1985 (Box 12)
  - Burger King--Asia-Pacific, 1985 (Box 12)
  - Burger King--Canada, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Burger King--Europe, 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Burger King--International reviews, 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Burger King--Latin America, 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Burger King--MMA (Managers' Monthly Assessments), 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - Carnation, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Chevron, undated (Box 13)
  - Client alignment list, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - Client information, 1983-1984 (Box 13)
  - Client lists, 1985 (Box 13)
  - De Beers, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - De Beers--International, 1980 (Box 13)
  - De Beers--MMA, 1983-1985 (Box 13)
  - Dole, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - Emery Air Freight, 1984-1986 (Box 13)
  - Ford, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - Ford--Asia-Pacific, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - Ford--Case history, 1984 (Box 13)
  - Ford--Europe, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - Ford--Latin America, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - Ford--MMA, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - Ford--Worldwide Supervisors' Meeting, 1984 (Box 13)
  - Gazelle, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Gillette, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Goodyear, 1960-1984 (Box 13)
  - Goodyear, 1983-1986; 3 folders (Box 14)
  - Goodyear--International, 1984; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Goodyear--MMA, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Goodyear--Presentations, 1984-1985; 4 folders (Box 14)
  - IBM, 1984-1986; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - IBM--Asia-Pacific, 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - IBM--Europe, undated (Box 15)
  - IBM--Japan, undated (Box 15)
  - IBM--Latin America, undated (Box 15)
  - IBM--Meeting with Warren Paul, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Jacobs Suchard, 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Kellogg, 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Kellogg--Asia-Pacific, 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Kellogg--Case history, 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Kellogg--Compensation, 1985; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Kellogg--Europe, 1984-1986 (Box 15)
  - Kellogg--Latin America, 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Kellogg--Meeting, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Kellogg--MMA, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Kellogg--Multinational costs, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Kellogg--National sales meeting, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Kellogg--South Africa, 1984-1986 (Box 16)
  - Kellogg--USA/Canada, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Kodak, 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Kodak--Leaders and Leadership, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Kodak--MMA, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Kraft, 1983-1985 (Box 16)
  - Kraft--Bill Ross, 1980-1985 (Box 16)
  - Kraft--Canada, 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Kraft--Latin America, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Kraft--Mexico, 1980-1981 (Box 16)
  - Kraft--MMA, 1983-1985 (Box 17)
  - Kraft--Presentations, 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Marine Corps, 1982-1983 (Box 17)
  - Mattel, 1983-1986; 5 folders (Box 17)
  - Mattel--Presentations, 1983-1985; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Nabisco, 1984-1986 (Box 18)
  - Nabisco--MMA, undated (Box 18)
  - Nestle, 1982-1985; 9 folders (Box 18)
  - Nestle, 1985-1986; 3 folders (Box 19)
  - Nestle--Coffee, presentations, 1984-1985 (Box 19)
  - Nestle--Frozen foods, 1984 (Box 19)
  - Nestle--MMA, 1984 (Box 19)
  - Nestle--Presentation, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Papa Giuseppi, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Parker Pen, undated (Box 19)
  - Pepsi, 1984-1986; 3 folders (Box 19)
  - Pepsi--Brand copy review, 1984 (Box 19)
  - Pepsi Challenge, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Pepsi Challenge case history, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Pepsi--Latin America, 1984-1986 (Box 20)
  - Pepsi--Pepsi Taste Goin' Over the Top campaign, 1984 (Box 20)
  - PepsiCo, 1983-1985; 2 folders (Box 20)
  - PepsiCo--Advertising management, 1985 (Box 20)
  - PepsiCo--MMA, 1985 (Box 20)
  - PepsiCo--Profile of JWT NY, 1985 (Box 20)
  - PepsiCo--Response to New Coke, 1985 (Box 20)
  - PepsiCo--Rod Malcolm briefing, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Philips, 1984-1986; 4 folders (Box 21)
  - Pillsbury, 1984 (Box 21)
  - Procter & Gamble--Bible on strategy, undated (Box 21)
  - Quaker Oats, 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Reynolds Metals, 1985 (Box 21)
  - RJ Reynolds, 1984-1986; 6 folders (Box 21)
  - RJ Reynolds--MMA, 1985 (Box 21)
  - Rolex, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Rolex--MMA, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Rolex--Print advertising, 1948-1981 and undated; 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Rowntree Mackintosh, 1983-1985 (Box 22)
  - Royal Canadian Mint, 1985 (Box 22)
  - R.T. French, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Safeway, 1984 (Box 22)
  - S.C. Johnson, 1984-1986 (Box 22)
  - Schering-Plough, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Scott Paper, 1986 (Box 22)
  - Seagrams, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Shiseido (JWT-Japan), 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Spalding, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Sprint, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Teachers, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Tetra Pak, 1985-1986 (Box 22)
  - Texaco, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Toshiba, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Twentieth Century Fox, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Uncle Ben's, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Unilever, 1975-1985; 3 folders (Box 22)
  - Unilever, 1983-1986 and undated; 11 folders (Box 23)
  - Unilever--Billings and profits, 1983 (Box 23)
  - Unilever--Business building plan, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Unilever--Case histories, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Unilever--Coordination, 1983-1985; 3 folders (Box 24)
  - Unilever--F.H. Faulding, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Unilever--London Office, 1983-1986; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Unilever--Lux Toilet Soap case history, 1984 (Box 24)
  - Unilever--MMA, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Unilever--Multinational business building plan, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Unilever--New York Office, 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - Unilever--Puerto Rico, 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - Unilever--Remuneration, 1983-1985 (Box 24)
  - Unilever--Remuneration, 1983-1985 (Box 25)
  - Unilver--S.C. Johnson, 1980-1985; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Unilever--Seminar and conferences, 1985 (Box 25)
  - Unilever--Slide presentation, 1984 (Box 25)
  - Unilever--Sunkist Japan, 1985 (Box 25)
  - Via Kelle, 1986 (Box 25)
  - Warner-Lambert, 1981-1986; 4 folders (Box 25)
  - Warner-Lambert--MMA, 1985 (Box 25)
  - Wedgwood, 1986 (Box 25)
- Presentations, Writings and Speeches, 1978-1986 and undated; 4
  - Ad Club breakfast, 1984 Nov. 20 (Box 25)
  - American Consumer: Myth and Reality, 1984; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Analysts meeting (Don Johnston), 1984; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Analyst presentation (Don Johnston), 1983 (Box 25)
  - Andy Awards 21st Annual Competition, undated (Box 25)
  - Andy Awards presentation, 1985 (Box 25)
  - Annual Meeting (Glen Dell, Don Johnston), 1986 (Box 25)
  - Bill Bernbach speech, 1984 (Box 25)
  - Brand Leadership California Portfolio Managers (Glen Dell, Don Johnston), 1985 (Box 26)
  - Case for New Growth Perspective (Security Analysts Meeting), 1981-1982; 5 folders (Box 26)
  - Cashel workshop, 1986; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Chicago client dinner multinational presentation, undated (Box 27)
  - Chicago Hospital Public Relations Society Communicator's Showcase, 1981 (Box 27)
  - Chicago Security Analysts Meeting, 1981 (Box 27)
  - Creativity Speech, undated (Box 27)
  - DuPont, 1984 (Box 27)
  - ECS presentation, undated (Box 27)
  - Essence of Positioning is Sacrifice (Joel Baumwoll), 1983 (Box 27)
  - European Managers Meeting, 1982 (Box 27)
  - Evolution of an Owl to a Hawk (Don Robertson), 1983 (Box 27)
  - Financial Analysts Meeting (Don Johnston), 1979; 3 folders (Box 27)
  - Frozen Foods presentation for Nestle, 1984 (Box 27)
  - George Black on advertising wearout, 1981-1986 (Box 27)
  - Global Approach to Marketing--And one way we can grow with it, undated (Box 27)
  - Global Marketing--And one way we can prosper from it, 1984 (Box 27)
  - Global Marketing From Now to the Twenty-First Century, undated (Box 27)
  - Global marketing management, 1986 (Box 27)
  - Global marketing trends, 1985; 3 folders (Box 28)
  - Global Media Commission (IAA), 1984-1986 (Box 28)
  - Globalism: A Mirage or a Market, 1986; 2 folders (Box 27)
  - H&R Block Cassette, 1980 (Box 28)
  - International presentation, undated (Box 28)
  - International transfers--Lessons learned, 1984 (Box 28)
  - Introduction to Epcot Meeting: Serving multinational clients at JWT, 1984; 2 folders (Box 28)
  - J. Walter Goes Global, undated (Box 28)
  - James Webb Young Seminar, 1983-1985 (Box 28)
  - Jonathon Miller, Stephen King Transcript, undated (Box 28)
  - Just to start the ball rolling (Advertising Education Foundation), 1986 (Box 28)
  - JWT: First Multinational Agency, undated (Box 28)
  - JWT booklet (What is advertising), 1986 (Box 28)
  - JWT credentials, undated (Box 28)
  - JWT/FDAF Chairman's Meeting (Wally O'Brien, Bucky Buchanan), 1982 (Box 28)
  - JWT Group: A Company of Companies, undated (Box 29)
  - JWT Group Analyst Meeting NY (Don Johnston, Herbert Eames), 1983 (Box 29)
  - JWT Group Financial Analysts Meeting (Don Johnston), 1980; 2 folders (Box 29)
  - JWT Group: Growing Through Brand Leadership:(Don Johnston, Jeremy Bullmore, Glen Dell), 1986 (Box 29)
  - JWT Group Security Analysts Meeting-New York, 1981 (Box 29)
  - JWT Multinational Client Services Plan, 1986 (Box 29)
  - JWT Toronto "The Industry's Most Creative Agency", 1983 (Box 29)
  - JWT USA: The Best in New York, 1983 (Box 29)
  - JWT Worldwide Account Services, undated (Box 29)
  - Latin American Managers Meeting, 1982 (Box 29)
  - Local Marketing, 1985 (Box 29)
  - Managing Change: The Role of Communications, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Managing in the Global Village, 1985 (Box 29)
  - Miscellaneous, 1982-1984 (Box 30)
  - Multinational Client Business Building Program, undated (Box 30)
  - Multinational Client Plan, 1984 (Box 30)
  - Multinational Progress Report, 1985 (Box 30)
  - Multinational Review, 1984 (Box 30)
  - Multinational Strategies, undated (Box 30)
  - Myth and Reality in the Advertising Business (Don Johnson, Alun Jones), 1978; 2 folders (Box 30)
  - National Quality Month Forum, 1985 (Box 30)
  - New Business Reports, undated (Box 30)
  - NY Analysts Meeting: Creativity, Growth, and the Bottom Line, 1985 (Box 30)
  - Old Bank Robbers' Guide to Where the New Money Is (Citicorp), undated (Box 30)
  - Operations Committee, 1985 (Box 30)
  - Outlook for '86 (Presentation to Paine Webber), 1985 (Box 31)
  - Philadelphia Analysts Meeting (Don Johnston, Herbert Eames), 1984 (Box 31)
  - Planning cycle, 1985 (Box 31)
  - Presentaton to New York Office, 1983 (Box 31)
  - Presentation to Security Analysts (Don Johnston, Herbrt Eames), 1982 (Box 31)
  - Quality Control, National Quality Month Forum, 1985 (Box 31)
  - Security Analyst and Stockholder Meetings, 1980 (Box 31)
  - Security Analysts Meeting, 1979-1980; 2 folders (Box 31)
  - Security Analysts Meeting (Don Johnston, Wayne Fickinger), 1981-1984; 3 folders (Box 32)
  - Some thoughts on beginning a career in advertising, undated (Box 32)
  - Speech for Joe O'Donnell, 1982 (Box 32)
  - Speech to JWT Personnel, 1981 (Box 32)
  - Werthein Breakfasts (Don Johnston, Glen Dell), 1985 (Box 32)
  - "What is an Advertising Idea" Workshop, 1986 (Box 32)
  - What is multinationality? Can it be cured?, 1985 (Box 32)
  - Worldwide Client Service Directors (Denis Lanigan), 1984 (Box 32)
  - Worldwide marketing: What does it mean to us, undated (Box 32)
  - Worldwide management trends, undated (Box 32)
  - Worldwide presentation, 1985 (Box 32)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1979-1985; 5
  - New York Analylsts Meeting: Creativity, Growth and the Bottom Line (Don Johnston, Glen Dell), 1985 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11620-Umatic-001)
    Scope and Contents
    17 commercials from JWT; 7 commercials from LGFE
  - Security Analysts Meeting (Don Johnston); 16 commercials, 1979 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11620-Umatic-002)
  - Security Analysts Meeting (Don Johnston; Herbert Eames speeches), 1983 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11620-CS-001)
  - Security Analysts Meeting (Don Johnston; Herbert Eames speeches), 1983 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11620-CS-002)
  - Financial Analysts Meeting (Don Johnston), 1980 (Box AV1, Audio-reel RL11620-RR-001)
  - Lord Geller Federico Einstein: Callard & Bowser "Help England Back on Its Feet" :60 radio spot to accompany Don Johnston speech to Analysts, 1983 (Box AV1, Audio-reel RL11620-RR-002)
  - Lord Geller Federico Einstein: Callard & Bowser "Help England Back on Its Feet" :60 radio spot to accompany Don Johnston speech to Analysts, 1983 (Box AV1, Audio-reel RL11620-RR-003)
  - JWT Group Financial Analysts Meeting commercial reel: 18 spots, 1980 (Reel 1, Film-reel RL11620-F16-001)